怎么了啊
What?
你吃完这么一份早餐
You realize a breakfast that size is meant for people
下地干活12小时都没问题
who are about to go work on a field for 12 hours.
反正后面也没事做 说不定我还真就下地了
Yeah,well,the rest of my day's open,so maybe that's what I'm gonna do.
赤脚踏板乐队要在舵手酒吧演出了
Guys,barefoot pedaler's playing at the wheelhouse.
不就是90年代的嬉皮风乐队嘛
A '90s hippie jam band.
我宁可听我挨枪子的声音
You know what I'd rather listen to?
而不乐意听他们唱歌
Myself being shot in the face.
别这样 Max
Oh,come on,max.
我们都很粉赤脚踏板呢
We have had some awesome nights with the pedalers.
我俩第一次约会 就是看他们的演出
We had one of our first dates at a pedaler show.
可不嘛
Yeah,we did.
他是那唯一的黑人
He was the only black guy there.
感觉自己像Rosa Parks 不过我没纠结一个座位而已
I was like rosa parks,except for something that didn't matter at all.
Rosa Parks 因拒绝给白人让座 引发了美国黑人民权运动
我真心觉得 咱该去看这次演出
Guys,I really think we need to go to this pedaler show.
这么多年 好不容易来一次芝加哥
I mean,they haven't played in chicago in years.
那我要带臭鸡蛋去
I will attend ironically.
能再看到Tommy 人家好幸福
It'd be great to see tommy again.
- 我了个去 又来了 - 没空听你讲完啦
- Oh,my god.Here it comes. - I don't think we have time for the whole story.
我跟你们说...
I'm just telling you. She's gonna go right
- 那是1999年的12月 - 开始了
- it was december '99. - Here it is.
差不多就是他们最后辉煌的那段日子
And it was right after pedaler got huge,but,like,before they got small again.
他是当时全世界最好的电吉他手 而我还是个懵懂少女
He was the best electric fiddler in the world,and I... I was just a girl.
我们那段缠绵 简直惊天地泣鬼神
We made love like warrior poets.
你还真做得出来
How do you even do that?
他后来邀请我参加巡演 但人家转天还有心理学期末考试
And then he invited me to tour with them,but I had an early morning psych final.
结果拿了B- 而且单身至今
Got a b-minus... And I'm still single.
groupie骨肉皮，是指那些疯狂追乐队，并且会和乐队成员发生性关系的粉丝
扯了这么多 就一句话 Penny就是个骨肉皮
Ridiculously long story short,penny was a groupie...
说不定现在还身染疱疹（性病）呢
And now she may or may not have the herp.
喂 我才不是骨肉皮呢
Wow,I was so not a groupie,okay?
他超耐我的 不信问Alex
He was super into me,and if you don't believe me,ask alex.
- 当然人不在 - 等等
- Who is not here. - Wait,guys.
你们是因为我 才没叫上Alex吗
Did you not invite alex because of me?
当然不是
no! No,not at all.
她有事儿
She was busy.
呃...我们得撤了
Uh,we gotta go.
真的得走了
We do. We do have to go.
我咖啡还没喝完呢
I haven't even finished my coffee yet.
没关系 带走嘛
Oh,it's okay.Take it to go.
烫着嘴了
I burned my mouth!
咋这么着急呢
Guys,what's the rush?
多玩会儿嘛
Aren't we gonna hang out?
- 我们得赶去... - 奶奶的葬礼
Oh,we actually have to go to,um... My grandma's funeral.
什么
What?
那是Tyler Perry的新电影
Uh,it's the new tyler perry movie.
Tyler Perry 好莱坞新晋黑人导演及演员
对对
Yeah,yeah.
回见
See you guys later.
- 回见 拜拜 - 回头见啊
- See ya! Bye! - See ya later,man.
大伙好
Hey,guys.
Alex
hey! Alex.
- 准备好吃早餐了吗 - 饿死了
- Ready for breakfast? - Starving.
<font color=#38B0DE>-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- -=http://ytet.org=</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 好心Justin 撒酷啦 阿吐 呸呸 怒怒 正经爫 狗肉 青柠 校对: 王棫垚 时间轴: 嘿嘿 双语合成兼压制：神秘人士</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>幸福终点站 第1季 第11集
<font color=#38B0DE>happy.endings Season 01 Episode 11</font>
咋了
What?
忘跟你们说了
Oh,I forgot to tell you guys.
赤脚踏板乐队要来演出 咱一起去吧
Barefoot pedaler's in town.We should all go.
我那晚没时间
You know what? I can't that night.
我还没说是哪天呢
I haven't told you what night it is yet.
- 你说了 - 没有
- Yes,you did. - no.
你说了
You did,yeah.
我好像忘拿钥匙...这是怎么了
I think I left my - My keys... What's going on?
- Dave - 你们不会吧
- Dave? - Is this what's happening now?
你们赶我走 因为还要见Alex
You guys rushed me out of breakfast because you have plans with alex?
没有 什么
No. What?
No.  What?
- 没有 什么 - 你单曲循环了 宝贝
- No. What? - You're in a loop,babe.You're in a loop.
真不敢相信 你们吃两份早餐
I cannot believe that you guys double-booked breakfast.
等等 这是什么意思
Wait. Wh-what's going on?
我不知道他在说些什么
I don't know what he's talking about.
我刚也在这 跟他们吃饭
I was just here,eating with them.
- 没有 - 有
- No. - Yes!
Dave 你吓到我们了 我们今天没见过你
Dave,you're scaring us.We haven't seen you today.
groundhog day 土拨鼠之日，是一部电影，讲循环的
真的 你当我脑残吗
Really? You're gonna try to "groundhog day" me?
Dave 你吓到我们了 我们今天没见过你
Dave,you're scaring us.We haven't seen you today.
你们吃两份早餐 是为了分开见我们吗
Wait.You double-booked breakfast just to keep us apart?
我们必须这么做
We had to.
跟你俩一起玩很痛苦
It has been brutal to hang out with you guys.
可能跟你俩的婚礼有关
Yeah,maybe it has something to do with what happened at your wedding.
不
no!
Dave
Dave?
对不起 我不行
I'm sorry. I can't do this.
我来了 很好
I'm coming.Okay.
也可能是别的原因 但其实不是
I mean,it could be something else,but... It's not.
好吧
Okay.
没错 但我们已经不纠结了
That happened... But we are moving on.
是吗 因为每次你俩碰一起
Are you? 'cause every time you're together,
芝麻点的事都能引起一顿暴吵
it seems like pretty much anything can trigger you into a huge fight.
晚上吃啥 中国菜还是披萨
So what are we doing tonight,guys - Chinese food or,uh,pizza pizza?
Alex不喜欢中国菜
Oh,alex does not like chinese food.
啥呀 我可没说过
What?I never said that.
只是咱以前总吃腰果鸡丁
It's just we always used to order cashew chicken all the time.
天天吃 是人都吃够了
I'm sorry if I got bored of eating cashew chicken a bajillion times.
- 真的 - 那个...
- Really? - So...
现在你想吃什么鸡都行了
Well,now you can have any kind of chicken you want.
糖醋鸡
You can have sweet and sour chicken.
柠檬鸡
You can have lemon chicken.
酒吧或健身房里遇到的脏“鸡” 都随你挑
You can have any filthy chicken that you pick up at a bar or meet at the gym,
因为我告诉你
'cause I'll tell you something.
你永远都吃不到腰果鸡了
You are never getting cashew chicken again.
我觉得他不是在说鸡
I - I don't think he's talking about chicken.
你是我的老友 你是我的姐妹
Okay,look,you are one of my oldest friends,and you are my sister,
我爱你们两个 但是分头行动比较方便
and I love you both,but it's just easier to do things... Separately.
分头行动 所以不只是早餐啊
Things? So it's not just breakfasts?
早餐 晚餐 喝饮料 看电影
Breakfasts,dinners,drinks,movies.
看了两遍"末日威途" 第二遍都不好笑了
And we had to rent "the road" twice,and it is not that funny the second time.
所以你们不愿意跟我去演唱会
So this is why you didn't want to go to the concert with me.
因为你们已经答应 跟Dave一起去了
'cause you were already going with dave.
太可笑了 我们相处很好
It's ridiculous.We're fine!
对吧 Dave
Right,dave?
- 对 - 对
- Yeah.Yeah. - Yeah.
事实上 我们很好
In fact,we are so fine,
我们应该一起去 赤脚踏板演唱会
that I-I think we should go to the pedaler concert together.
- 真的 - 好主意
- Really? - That is a great idea.
你们觉得没问题吗
You guys would be cool with that?
- 是啊 - 当然啦
- yes! - Yes!Of course.
- 好吧 - 好
- All right. - Okay. Okay,cool.
太棒了
This is gonna be awesome.
太糟了
This is gonna be terrible.
他们说没问题
I mean,they say that they're fine,
但是一点小事就会引发大吵
and then one small thing is gonna trigger them again.
而且他们总是让我站队
Yeah,and they always try to get me to take sides.
问你个问题 Brad
Let me ask you a question,brad.
你觉得腰果鸡丁很难吃吗
Do you think that cashew chicken is boring?
还是说腰果鸡丁很好吃
Or do you think that cashew chicken is a total catch
任何吃到它的女人 都应该觉得幸运
that any lady would be lucky enough to eat and,in fact,
它比很多名菜都好吃
cashew chicken passed up on a lot of hot,smokin' ass?
是啊
Oh,right.
因为腰果鸡丁用的是皇家鸡
Because cashew chicken is a completely loyal chicken!
我对腰果过敏
I'm actually allergic to nuts.
我不想要Dave和Alex同时出现
I don't want dave and alex there.
再见到Tommy 就已经够疯狂了
Already gonna be a crazy enough night when I see tommy again.
- 老天 - 我们之间是天雷勾动地火
- Oh,my god. - Our chemistry was explosive.
就像是梁祝
It was like whitney and bobby.
你是说像梁启超和祝枝山吗
You mean eli whitney and justin bobby?
他俩也一点关系都没有
'cause those are also two people that mean nothing to each other.
如果我只是路人 那歌曲"Jenny"怎么解释
If I didn't mean anything to him,who's the song "jenny" about?
给叫Jenny的女生写的
A girl named jenny?
Jenny就是指Penny 好好想想
No,jenny is penny. Think about it.
字母J 旋转再合拢 得到什么
Take the "j," flip it,close the loop,what do you have?
- 小写的b - 不是
- Lowercase "b"? - no.
- 小写的d - 不
- A lowercase "d"? - No.
上下翻转
Flip it the other way.
- 小写的q - 是Penny啦
- "Q. - no.Penny.
烂透了
This sucks.
我只想好好玩乐一下
I mean,I just wanna go and party
不用去想 怎么同时顾好Dave和Alex
and not have to worry about babysitting dave and alex.
我已经记入手机备忘了
Now I already have it in my phone.
周五晚上9点 大爆炸什么时候发生待定
Friday night,9:00 p.m. Till question mark-rage.
这可不是普通的小爆
And I do not mean a small rage.
而是核爆一样的大爆炸
I mean,like,mardi gras-style rage.Okay?
乌拉拉呱呱呱
Laissez les bons temps rouler!
法语啦 意思是嗨到彻底
it's "let the good times roll.
Jane喝高 就变身为库克船长了
" When jane gets drunk,she turns into a creole riverboat captain.
- 起航 - 够了
- Guar-on-tee! - That's it.
- 不许再看"真爱如血"了 - Jane没错
- No more "true blood" for you. - No,jane's right.
如果他们去了演唱会 咱就别想乐了
If they come to the concert,we're not gonna have any fun.
他们会继续上演二人转的
It's just gonna turn into another episode of the dave and alex show.
那咱这样吧
I think we know what we need to do.
Brad和Jane没法去演唱会了
So brad and jane can't go to the show.
因为Jane食物中毒呕吐不停
Jane's throwing up 'cause she's got food poisoning,
Brad看到别人呕吐 他自己也吐了
and brad's throwing up because he can't see other people throw up,
他们上演家庭呕吐大戏呢
so it's a general puke spiral over there.
Penny和Max也电话我了 说不能去
Penny and max called and said they can't come either.
Penny被锁在商场里了 Max捡到个小孩
Penny got locked in a mall,and max found a baby.
这也编得太离奇了
What? That's ridiculous.
借口都找不到个好的
They can't even come up with good excuses.
他们在躲我们而已
They just don't wanna see us.
烦啊 我真的很想去看演出
Yeah,this sucks,'cause I really wanted to see the show.
我也是
Yeah,me,too.
要不咱一起去吧
Maybe we should just go.
- 除非... - 没...
- Unless... - no.
除非你不想和我一起去
Unless you don't wanna hang,just you and me.
没啊 咱一起去吧
No,no,we should totally... Go... Together.
一起开车上路
We should go on a road trip together.
去参观美国所有棒球场
We could see every ballpark in america.
还是先说演唱会吧
Uh,why don't we just start with a concert?
好吧
Yeah. Okay.
Hi. Hey.
hey.
All right.
咱不会尴尬的
This isn't gonna be weird at all.
是啊 肯定正常 除了我还要强调"正常"
No,it's gonna be totes normal... Except that I just said "totes.
走吧 咱找乐子去 让他们羡慕嫉妒恨
" Come on.Let's show 'em what a good time they're missing.
好
- Okay. - Okay.
- 茄子 - 茄子
- Ready? - Yeah.
还不错 真想欣赏他们看到这彩信时的表情
Nice.Wish I could see their faces when they get this.
对啊
Yeah.
这么巧呀 我们刚收到你们的彩信
Hey,guys.We just got your text.
你们在搞什么飞机
What's going on?
先是对咱撒谎 然后抛下我们来演唱会了
First you lie to us,and then you show up without us?
看起来是这样的 辩解一下啊
Well,I know this looks bad,but in our defense,
我们以为你们不会来
we didn't think you guys were gonna come here.
老大 能找个好点的辩解吗
Dude,how is that a defense?
没想到你们俩会一起来啊
I can't believe the two of you guys came together.
没错 都告诉你X遍了 我俩好着呢
Yeah,we did,because we're fine,like I told you a bajillion times.
你懂的吧 没有X遍这个说法
You do know that that's not a real number,right?
你还老说
'cause you use it a lot.I just...
也没bajina（vagina阴道）的说法
Neither is bajina.Not a real word.
同学 拜托
Guys,come on.
一起看赤脚踏板 不正好让我俩和解嘛
What better way to bring us back together than to go to a pedaler show?
让我们回到从前
I mean,come on.Let's be the college us.
对
Yeah.
谁说我们嗨不起来
Who dat say we ain't gonna have some fun?
谁说的 谁说的
Who dat? Who dat?
谁说我们嗨不起来
Who dat say we ain't gonna have some fun?
谁说的 谁说的
Who dat?! Who dat?!
悠着点 James Carville
Pump the brakes,james carville.
James Carville 美国民主党政策顾问 出名的多动症
白人染个彩虹头 喝
white guy with rainbow dreads.Drink!
腋毛姐
Oh,girl with armpit hair.
腿毛姐 喝了 贱人们
Girl with leg hair.Jon lovitz!Drink,bitches!
真不知道这游戏到底怎么玩
I have no idea how you win this game...
但我敢肯定Jane领先
But I am positive jane's in the lead.
- 领先! - 领先!
- In the lead! - In the lead!
怎么你比我还醉
How are you more drunk than me?
因为之前就喝了点
'cause I pre-gamed.
亲爱的 换个新游戏吧
Okay,babe,let's play a new game.
名字叫 弄点吃的給老婆
It's called "feed my wife some food.
我去给你弄点吃的吧 亲爱的
" I'm gonna grab you something.Okay,honey?
要离舞台近点就好了
I wish we were closer!
其实我还挺喜欢后排冷清的感觉
Oh,I kinda like chilling out back here,you know?
我知道你们的意思了
I - I hear you guys.
想要我去后台找Tommy
Want me to go backstage,talk to tommy,
看他能不能给我们找个靠前的位置
and see if he can get us a table up front?
你幻听吧
No one said that at all.
收到消息 表示有压力
Message received.Arm twisted.
另外 我想让他知道我在场
Besides,I wanna let him know i'm here
这样他唱"Jenny"时 可能会让我上台
just in case he wants to pull me up onstage when they sing "jenny.
她很快就会恢复正常 是吧
" You guys think she'll come to her senses,right?
我就不用整晚看着Penny了
I don't have to be on penny patrol all night?
姐看起来还像学生吧
I still look 20,right?
- 明白 - 没错吧
- I got it. - See?
大家现在多嗨啊
We're having fun!
我们相处得越来越好了 不愉快都结束了
Yes,and it's only getting better.It's called closure.
遗忘掉婚礼...
The wedding is behind us..
退回了所有的礼物 写感谢信 完了
I sent back all the gifts.Wrote the thank-you notes.Done.
等等 寄了感谢信吗
Wait.You sent out the thank-you notes?
写了什么
What'd you say?
我是按照Emily Post的建议去做的
Oh,I just-I put down what emily post recommended in this situation-"
Emily Post 美国礼仪女王
"婚礼未举行 因此而退回您贴心的礼物"
we are returning your thoughtful gift because the wedding didn't take place.
你不觉理由没解释清楚吗
" kind of vague,don't you think?
就像说肯尼迪在没能完成在达拉斯访问
I mean,that's like saying the rest of j.f.k.'s tour of dallas did not take place.
那你觉得我该写什么
What was I supposed to write?
触发点
There's the trigger.
战争一触即发了
Here come the fireworks.
没没
No.No. No,no.
- 怎么了 - 我们很好
- What's going on? - We're fine. We're fine.
俺们不在外晒自家丑闻
We are not airing our dirty laundry in public.
对 不晒丑闻 亲爱的 (laundry也有待洗衣物的意思)
Yeah,no more laundry,mon cher.
干净小内都叠好了放抽屉里
Her undies are clean,and they're stacked in the drawer
袜子也都团成小团
next to the socks which are... In the little balls.
都是干净的衣服
Clean clothes!
姑娘 赶紧把这个玉米素饼吃下去
Woman,put this veggie burrito in you now.
我喝高了
I'm drunk.
姐是老手了，就装作你是工作人员一样
I've done this a million times.Just act like you belong.
闭嘴 Steven Tyler
shut up,steven tyler.
Steven Tyler 美国歌手 美偶新评委
不 你知道我喜欢打麻将
No,you know I love mah-jongg.
麻将
Mah-jongg?
好了 我要挂了 我得去一趟后台
Um,steven tyler,okay,I gotta go 'cause I gotta head backstage and-oh.
没有通行证 哪都不许去
You're not going anywhere without a pass.
嗨 帅哥
Hey,listen,hi,handsome.
我要告诉你一点小秘密
You know,let me let you in on a little secret.
我和Tommy 就是那个弹电吉他的
Um,me and tommy,you know,the electric fiddle player?
我们之间有过一段，有性关系的一段
We have a history,and it's a sex history.
好了 你的计划就是让大家都尴尬死吗
Okay,is your plan to make things super-awkward for everybody?
这一点都不尴尬
It's not awkward.
事实上 很尴尬
Actually,it is.
能给我四杯啤酒吗
Hey,can i,uh,get four beers?
还有我的醉汉朋友让我问一句 你们有三明治吗
And I promised my super-drunk friend that I would ask-
Do you guys have po'boys?
关门放狗
Shut the front door!
Dave Rose在这儿
Dave rose!
在酒吧碰到D.Rose诶
D.Rose in the hizzy!
怎么样啊 老兄
- What's up,bro? - Hey.
- Brody Daniels - 最近好吗 兄弟
Brody daniels. What's up,dude?
- 好久不见 - 好久不见
- What's up,man? - Yeah,man.
天啊 你被关进去后就没见了 他们说你...
Oh,jeez,I haven't seen you since you got arrested for...
闯进了Kelly Kirkpatrick的宿舍
Breaking into kelly kirkpatrick's dorm room!
兄弟 爽啊
Bro,yeah,man!Boom.
娶了她 更爽的是
Married her.Boom.Boom.
还生了两个孩子
Two kids.
事事顺心 还得到了一份园艺工作
Doing good,man.Got this landscaping thing going.
别客气 需要什么景观石尽管找我
It's cool,man.Let me know if you need any,like,light-up rocks or whatever,man.
谢了 兄弟 那太棒了
Yeah,thanks.Man,that's awesome.
祝贺你那个什么石的工作
Congrats on the rocks thing.
谢谢
Thanks so much.
我看到网上看了你的婚礼视频
I saw that youtube thing,man.That wedding thing?
你够玩闹啊
Dude,that was a real kick in the downstairs stuff,bro.
谢了 老兄 承蒙夸奖
No,thanks,man.I - I appreciate that.
别谦虚了 我很欣赏
Dude,no,man,I appreciated it.
我转发给好友 他们也很欣赏
Everyone on my e-mail list appreciated it.
Jane的三明治吃完了
hey.Jane's over the po'boys,
现在她又想打电话给她前男友们了
but now she wants to call all her ex-boyfriends.
你们俩在约会
You're hanging out?
你和落跑新娘在约会
You hang out with the girl that snipped your speed bag,bro?
- 啥 - 老兄
- What? - Dude.
事实上 我们复合了
Uh,actually... We are back together.
没错
That's right.
我回心转意了 以前的我实在太蠢了
I came crawling back.I was an idiot.
Dave是好男人 好伴侣
Dave's an amazing man and an incredible lover.
他绝对是顶级好情人
Really good lover.Stamos good.
- 所以你俩又复合了 - 是啊
- So you guys are back together? - Yeah.
真酷
Uh,cool.
这样的话 那段视频就没那么有趣了 但还是恭喜你们
Makes the video less funny,I guess,but,uh,congrats.
祝好 D.Rose
Peace,d.Rose.
躲过一劫啊 谢谢
Dodged a bullet there.Thank you.
你想啥呢
What were you thinking?
我不想让他嘲笑我们
I didn't like the way he was laughing at us.
他不是在嘲笑我们 Alex
He wasn't laughing at us,alex.
他是在嘲笑我 好吧
He was laughing at me,all right?
每个人都是在嘲笑我
Everybody is laughing at me.
我以为我是在帮你
I thought I was helping you.
是是 你在帮我
Oh,yeah,yeah,you helped me.
是呀 您让哥变得这么出名
You helped me get famous.
让哥脸面无存
You helped me get my speed bag cut.
让哥刷爆信用卡来准备婚礼 结果婚礼却吹了
You helped me max out all my credit cards for a wedding that never happened!
你俩怎么了 发生什么了
What up,players?What's going on?
大家都很嗨吧
Everybody having a good time?
拜托！
Oh,come on!
你对我还有怨气 还来个什么啊
if you're still so mad at me,why did you even come?
你已经说过没事了
You said you were fine.
Brad 他说过的吧
Did he not say he was fine,brad?
反正你俩都说话了
He said some things.You said some things.
说真的 我就是来给媳妇拿杯咖啡
Really just came here to get some coffee for my wife.
我觉得我已经没事了
You know what?I thought that I was fine.
我真的很想一切如常
I really wanna be fine.
但我想着 Jane说得没错
But I think that jane is kinda right here.
我开始还好 但突然之间 就有导火索挑起了我的怒火
I'll feel okay,and then all of a sudden,something will trigger my anger.
就是个蠢蛋哥看了网络视频嘛
So one jackass frat boy saw the youtube video.
他叫啥Brody 听着就是个路人
His name's brody.No one with that name has ever mattered.
不仅一个哥们看见了 好吧
No,not just one frat boy,al. Okay?
还有咱们的亲朋好友 还有很多陌生人
All of our friends and thousands of complete strangers.
大家已经不满足于观看了 都开始搞创作了
And they're not just watching it anymore.They're getting creative.
给她看看 Brad
Oh,yeah.Yeah.Show her,brad.
- 哥们 我还等着咖啡呢 - 你行啊
- Still waiting on that coffee,bro,anytime. - All right,you know what?
我也有 有几个天杀的西班牙DJ
I got it.Some spanish d.j.
弄了个remix
Decided to make a little auto-tune.
不要
No!
Alex Alex Alex
alex,alex,alex
这咋回事儿
what's happening here?
你说过 你说过 你说过
you told me,you told me,you told me
跟他做 一点儿都不爽
that the sex was bad
我不能这样做
I can't do this
真恶心
that's awful.
- 挺上口的 - 是啊
- Catchy,though. - Yeah.
其实大家隔天就会爱上其他热门视频的
Okay,uh,but,you know,people will move on to the next
hot viral video in,like,a day.
像什么 胖子卡在门里啊什么的
Some fat kid'll get stuck in a door.
你为什么总是想要洗白这件事 搞得跟没发生过一样
Why do you keep trying to whitewash this as if this thing never happened?
因为它很糟糕 并且错在我
Because it was horrible,and it was my fault.
很感激你对我和Brad这样说
I appreciate you saying that to me and brad,al.
但是 你知道吗
Okay? But you know what?
伤害已经造成了
The damage is done,okay?
而且目前还没办法弥补 所以...
And there's no taking it back now,so...
咖啡好了
Coffee.
说得有点伤人哈
Stings a bit.
别走 Brad 我该怎么办
No,wait,brad.What do I do?
拜托 帮帮我
Please,help me.
说实话 你让他熟人面前颜面无存
Honestly,you embarrassed the guy in front of everyone he's ever known.
如果你能在所有人面前
It'd be great if there was,like,
大胆澄清真相 那样也挺好的
some big way for you to set the record straight in front of all of them,
但生活不是一出浪漫喜剧
but,unfortunately,we're not in a romantic comedy,so...
Jenny
jenny
Jenny 这是你的姓名
jenny,that's your name
没人像你一样水灵
there's no girl that's quite the same
唱的就是姐
that's me.
他为我而写的
He wrote - he wrote that song about me.
你叫Jenny吗
Is your name jenny?
- 傻眼了吧 - 艺术是有虚构的
- Check and mate. - Has no one heard of poetic license?
你听说过泰瑟枪吗
You ever heard of a taser license?
那是个真家伙
Okay,all right.That's real.
天啊 那就是他
Oh,my god.That's him.
Tommy
Tommy! Hey,tommy!
有事吗
Yeah?
我是Penny 也可以说是Jenny
It's penny. Jenny.
还记得在基诺沙吗
Remember kenosha?
我们在你的巡演巴士车顶上喝酒 一起度过千禧年之夜
We spent the night of y2k together on top of your tour bus drinking box wine?
我们还说过
Remember we stayed up all night talking about
不知道第二天早上银行卡还能刷嘛
whether or not we'd be able to use our a.t.m. Cards in the morning?
你还说过你爱我 想起来了吗
And you told me you loved me?
对不起 宝贝 我...
Yeah,I'm sorry,babe.It's...
为我伤过心的女孩海了去了 很难都记住
It's hard to keep track of all the broken hearts.
爱你哦
One love?
天啊
Oh,my god.
等一下 Penny
Wait,penny.
哥们 给你
Here you go,dude.
拜托 这不是我的外套 你秀逗了
Come on,man.In what world is that my coat?
我不能就这么让Dave走了 我得做点儿什么
I can't let dave leave.I gotta do something.
Tommy根本就不记得我了
Tommy didn't even remember me.
同志们 咱们走吧
Guys,can we just go,please?
我们不能走 Brad说得对
We can't go,okay? Brad's right.
我有必要站在台上澄清一下
I need to get up on that stage and make a big speech,
因为生活就像一出浪漫喜剧
because life is like a romantic comedy.
不对 我说生活不是浪漫喜剧
No,I said life is not like a romantic comedy.
也许它是呢
Maybe it is.
她要干什么
What is she doing?
不知道 可她的眼神很疯狂
I don't know,but she's got crazy eyes.
对不起 借过
Excuse me.Move,please.
Dave 等一下
Dave,wait!
大家好 我要澄清一件事...
Everyone,I have to set the record straight on-aah!
我了个去 Alex
Damn,son!Alex! Al!
你到底在干啥
What are you doing,man?!
Alex
Alex! Alex!
该死 他倒下了
Damn!He went down!
好好笑呀
Hilars.
你好啊 Tommy
What's up,tommy?
我们认识你吗
Do we know you?
认识啊 时间是"从现在开始"
Yes,you do,if the time frame is "from now on,"
地点在"你的噩梦中"
and the place is "your nightmares.
什么
" excuse me?
我来这儿 是为了Penny
I'm here for penny.
谁
who?
Jenny 兄弟 你一定记得她
Jenny? Penny.I know you remember her,bro.
记得 就是外面那个意淫的疯女孩
Yeah.The crazy girl from out front that thinks I'm in love with her.
是啊 那个爱意淫的疯女孩
Yeah.The cr-the crazy chick that thinks.
天哪 她意淫的哈
Oh,god.She thinks it.
那要怎么解释 你在2003年4月 接受日本"打虎"杂志采访时说
Then how come in april of 2003 did you tell japanese "tiger beat"
你经历过最美好的约会是千禧年
that the best date of your life was on your tour bus
在基诺沙巡演巴士车顶 边喝酒边看日出
during y2k drinking box wine watching the sun rise over kenosha?
这意味着你和Penny的事是真的
That means that you and penny had a real thing going on.
也可能意味着 你和Penny都读那本杂志
Or that means that penny reads japanese "tiger beat" and... So do you.
我确实读
I do read it...
只读封面上有你们的那几期
When you guys are on the cover.
我真的爱赤脚踏板
I mean,I love barefoot pedaler.
我会告诉别人 我不喜欢你们 因为我怕流言蜚语
Do I tell people I don't like you 'cause I care what people think about me?
毕竟没有同志嬉皮士
Yeah,and 'cause there are no gay hippies.
千真万确 这很难堪
Double true.It's embarrassing.
Mahesh 我买了你的个人专辑
Mahesh,I bought your solo album.
没人会买你的个人专辑
No one bought your solo album.
J Rock 你出戒毒所的时候 我就在门口
J - rock,I was there when you got out of rehab,
举着"明天会更好"的标语
holding up the sign,"you'll get 'em next time.
我真的是你们的超级脚粉
" I mean,I'm a huge pedal head.
至少曾经是
At least I was...
直到你伤害了世界上最酷的女生
Until you broke the heart of the coolest girl in the world.
我要出去了 我走了
I'm outta here. I am gone.
你们即将失去头号粉丝
Number one fan,peacin' out!
在此之前 能不能帮我签个名
Just as soon as you sign one of these.Could you just...
随便哪一张 谁能给我签
Uh,one of these cds for me,anybody?
我再稍微拿几个纪念品
And I'm just gonna grab some souvies-souvenirs.
有谁愿意帮我签名吗
Anyone wanna sign that?
那电枪电得我浑身都疼
That taser hurt every part of my body.
我知道 我都蛋疼了
I know. I can feel it in my chundle.
我知道这么问有点尴尬 你尿裤子了吗
I know this is embarrassing,but did you pee yourself?
我还以为只有我尿裤了
I thought I was the only one.
- 是只有你 我只是问问 - 我也只是问问
- You are.I was just asking. - I was just asking.
我不知道自己怎么想的 竟然会跑上台去
I don't know what I was thinking,getting up there.
我不知道怎么做才能改正 但我尽力了
I mean,I just... I don't know how to make it right,but I'm trying to.
我知道 谢谢 Alex
I know you are,alex.Thank you.
我不明白的是 既然你这么生我的气
What I don't understand is why you got up there,
为什么还会上台来
even though you're mad at me.
这是因为不管我们之间发生了什么
Well,it's 'cause no matter what happens between us,
我永远会照顾你 Al
i'll always look out for you,al.
让一让
Make room.
这个蠢货刚才想偷贝司手的衣服
This jackass just stole the shirt off the bass player.
是啊 快走开 你不能再蹂躏我了
Yeah,walk away.You won't have any more of me.
- 不要 - 不要啊
- Don't do that. - Don't do that,man.
你知道哪里怪异吗
hey. Ird,man?
什么
What?
这就是我梦想中的夜晚啊
This is exactly how I thought the night would go.
标准三连击
It's your standard triple-tase resolution.
是啊 我觉得挺好的
yep.I think it's nice.
不管发生了什么 我们永远在彼此身旁
No matter what happens,we're always here for each other.
- Penny - Tommy
- Penny! - Tommy!
Penny 对不起
Penny! I'm sorry.
我当然记得你
Of course I remembered you.
事实上 我跟成百上千的女人上过床
The truth is,you're probably one of the only girls that I remember at all,
有时候一次两三个
and I've slept with thousands and thousands of women,
我可能只记得你了
sometimes two,three at a time.
全世界唯一一个
You know,all over the world.
说真的 你让我心碎
To be honest... You broke my heart.
我就知道 "Jenny"那首歌是写给我的
I knew you wrote "jenny" about me.
不 我老婆叫Jenny
No. I-I wrote "jenny" about my wife jenny.
别管他了 Penny
But forget about that.Come on,pen.What do you think?
演唱会结束后 有一班开往克诺沙的巴士
The bus is heading to kenosha after the show.
我们可以去看日出
We're gonna be there by sunrise.
来吗
You in?
当然不
Of course not.
你刚承认了 你跟成百上千的女人上过床
You just admitted to sleeping with thousands of women.
再加上你已经结婚了 而且你要搭巴士去威斯康辛
Plus you're married,and you're going to wisconsin by bus,
这所有事情中有两件事是让我性奋的
and only two of those things are turn-ons.
再见 Tommy
Good-bye,tommy.
搞什么啊
Oh,what?
该死
Damn.
不 我得走了
No. I have to go.
哪两件事是让你性奋的
So which two were the turn-ons?
淑女是不会说的
A lady never tells.
威斯康辛和巴士
Wisconsin and buses.
- 我的天哪 - 我也是
- Oh,my god. - Me,too!
Jenny 这是你的姓名
jenny,that's your name
没人像你一样水灵
there's no girl that's quite the same
Penny
penny!
Penny 我最亲密的朋友
penny,penny,penny,you're my closest friend
矮油 你为我写了首歌
oh,you wrote a song about me.
我愿意与你相伴 直到世界尽头
wanna be with you till the bitter end
太动人了
that is so sweet.
你的小腿肚是男人里最粗壮的
got the bigst calves I've seen on a man
等等 这歌词不像是我呀
wait.I don't-I don't see how that lyric applies.
确实不像你
Oh,it doesn't.
是我在非主流商店认识了一个叫Kenny的人
Uh,it's for this guy kenny that I met at a spencer's gifts.
我特意把首字母改掉了
Uh,I changed the first letter of the names just so...
你对他真好
Oh,how nice for him.
是啊
I think so.
Penny 我最亲密的朋友
penny,penny,penny,you're my closest friend
我愿意与你相伴 直到世界尽头
wanna be with you till the bitter end
尽头
end
你的小腿肚是所有男人里最粗壮的
got the biggest calves for a man
就这样了咩
that's it?
目前只写到这儿
It's where I'm at right now.